

Personal Details

Name Sneha S

Address 6/90 Honnathalai Village, Billicombai Post, The Nilgiris 643214 Phone number 7639838243

Email snehaabi676@gmail.com

Interests

Drawing Recent Hobby (Learning on StockMarket)

Sneha S

Management Associate with more than 3 years of experience in Bancassurance. Recognized for the ability to communicate with customers and provide exceptional services that ensures client retention. Proven ability to increase sales through upselling techniques as well as implement additional processes that drives profitability.

Work experience

Associate Key Relationship Manager

Standard Chartered Bank - Bancassurance

Oct 2020 - Present

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited

- Assists and provides investment recommendations to the HNI customers of **Standard Chartered Bank** by focusing on the customer needs. Also holds the experience of working for ICICI Bank Wealth Management.
- Also focuses on generating high revenue to the bank by selling banking products like Mutual Funds, NFO, Business Loans, Personal Loans, Fixed Deposits, Credit Cards etc as per the requirements.
- Provides customer satisfaction by providing the services on time which promotes additional businesses and references.
- Have overachieved the assigned target and rewarded with many recognitions and promotions.

HR Associate - Internship

May 2020 - Jul 2020

Ernst & Young, Bangalore

- Worked as a part of Recruiting Team
- Recruited experienced and entry-level associates for various job profiles based on the Job description. Managed the operational hiring process starting from sourcing screening and interviewing of candidates, up to scheduling of interviews.
- Coordinated on the complete onboarding process.
- Attracts applicant by placing job advertisements; contacting recruiters using Naukri.

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Commerce PSG College of Arts and Science, Coimbatore	Jun 2015 - May 2018
Master of Business Administration (MBA) Bharathiar University, Coimbatore	Aug 2018 - May 2020
HSC Stanes Higher Secondary School, Coonoor	Jun 2014 - May 2015
SSLC Mountain Home and Junior College, Coonoor	Jun 2013 - Apr 2014

Skills

Communication Skills
Interpersonal Skills
Problem Solving Skills
Observing Skill

Courses

Banking & Insurance

Jun 2015 - May 2016

• The major objective of this course is to learn on the basics of Banking and Insurance and also on how the current banking sector works.

Organizational Behaviour

Aug 2018 - May 2019

Bharathiar University

The main objective of this course is to set up an organizational culture, hiring the best people and creating meaningful connections among them, resolving the conflicts, developing the qualities of the employees, and establish a firm and clear leadership chain.